A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1977-1981, RG 33 FA1503
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1977-1981; 33
  - Welfare, 1977-1981; 33
    - American Red Cross (Box 668, Folder 2-3)
    - Center for Community Change (Box 668, Folder 4)
    - Community Service Society (Box 669, Folder 1)
    - United Funds - A-Z (Box 669, Folder 2)
    - United Funds - United Way of Tri-State (Box 669, Folder 3)
    - USO (Box 669, Folder 4)
    - USO - Metropolitan New York (Box 670, Folder 1)
    - Tune-In (Box 670, Folder 2)
    - Visiting Nurse of New York (Box 670, Folder 3)
    - Work in America Institute, Inc. (Box 670, Folder 4, Box 671, Folder 1)
    - Animals - A-Z (Box 671, Folder 2)
    - Animals - American Society for Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (Box 671, Folder 3)
    - Animals - Animal Welfare Institute (Box 672, Folder 1)
    - Animals - Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (Box 672, Folder 2)
    - Blind - A-Z (Box 672, Folder 3)
    - Community Centers - A-D (Box 672, Folder 4)
    - Community Centers - E-Z (Box 673, Folder 1)
    - Community Centers - Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association (Box 673, Folder 2)
    - Community Centers - Fifth Avenue Community Center of Harlem Inc. (Box 673, Folder 3)
    - Crime Prevention - A-Z (Box 673, Folder 4)
    - Crime Prevention - Eisenhower Foundation for Prevention of Violence (Box 674, Folder 1)
    - Day Nurseries - A-Z (Box 674, Folder 2)
    - Family Counseling - A-Z (Box 674, Folder 3)
    - Family Counseling - Family Service Association of America (Box 674, Folder 4)
    - Family Counseling - Family Service of Nassau County (Box 674, Folder 5)
    - Handicapped - A-Z (Box 675, Folder 1-3)
    - Handicapped - International Center for the Disabled (Box 676, Folder 1)
    - Handicapped - ICD Rehabilitation and Research Center (Box 676, Folder 2)
    - Handicapped - ICD - Dinner re David Rockefeller, 1981 October 14 (Box 676, Folder 3)
    - Handicapped - Homes - A-Z (Box 676, Folder 4)
    - (Native American) Indians - A-N (Box 677, Folder 1-3)
    - (Native American) Indians - N-Z (Box 678, Folder 1)
    - (Native American) Indians - American Indian Institute (Box 678, Folder 2)
    - (Native American) Indians - Institute for Career and Vocational Training (Box 678, Folder 3)
    - (Native American) Indians - Institute for the Development of Indian Law, Inc. (Box 678, Folder 4)
    - (Native American) Indians - Native American Rights Fund (Box 678, Folder 5)
    - Legal - A-Z (Box 679, Folder 1-2)
    - Legal - Legal Aid Society (Box 679, Folder 3)
    - Legal - Southern Coalition on Jails and Prisons (Box 679, Folder 4)
    - Musicians (Box 679, Folder 5)
    - Orphans (Box 680, Folder 1)
  - Women (Role of), 1977-1981; 34
    - Women (Role of) - A-N (Box 680, Folder 2-4)
    - Women (Role of) - O-W (Box 681, Folder 1-3)
    - Catalyst (Box 681, Folder 4)
    - Ms. Foundation for Women, 1978-1981 (Box 681, Folder 5)
    - National Congress of Neighborhood Women (Box 682, Folder 1)
    - Women's Action Alliance, Inc. (Box 682, Folder 2)
    - National Women's Health Network (Box 682, Folder 3)
  - Youth, 1977-1981; 35
    - Youth - A-C (Box 682, Folder 5)
    - Youth - C-M (Box 683, Folder 1-4)
    - Youth - N-Z (Box 684, Folder 1-3)
    - Boys Clubs of America (Box 684, Folder 4)
    - Boys Clubs of New York - Laurance S. Rockefeller (Box 684, Folder 5)
    - Boys Clubs of New York (Box 685, Folder 1)
    - Boys Clubs of St. Croix (Box 685, Folder 2)
    - Boys Scouts of America - A-Z (Box 685, Folder 3-4)
    - Children's Aid Society (Box 685, Folder 5)
    - Children's Cultural Foundation (Box 685, Folder 6)
    - Citizen's Committee for Children of New York (Box 686, Folder 1-2)
    - Covenant House (Box 686, Folder 3)
    - Girls Scout of America (Box 686, Folder 4)
    - Printed Material (Box 687, Folder 1)
    - Putnam's Children Center (Box 687, Folder 2)
    - Save the Children Federation (Box 687, Folder 3)
    - Voluntary National Service System (Box 687, Folder 4)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) (Box 687, Folder 5)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - Greater New York (Box 687, Folder 6)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - Contributions (Box 687, Folder 7)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) (Box 688, Folder 1)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board (Box 688, Folder 2)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board - Contributions (Box 688, Folder 3)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board - Board of Trustees (Box 688, Folder 4)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board - Minutes-Meetings (Box 688, Folder 5)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board - Printed Matter (Box 688, Folder 6)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board - Finances (Box 689, Folder 1)
    - Youth Camps (Box 689, Folder 2)
    - Youth Camps - Fresh Air Fund (Box 689, Folder 3)
    - Youth Project (Box 690, Folder 1)
    - Youth Project - A-C (Box 690, Folder 2-4)
    - Youth Project - D-Z (Box 691, Folder 1-2)
    - Youth Project - Campaign for Political Rights (Box 691, Folder 3)
    - Youth Project - Contributions (Box 691, Folder 4, Box 692, Folder 1)
    - Youth Homes - A-Z (Box 692, Folder 2)
  - X-Y-Z, 1977-1981; 36
    - X-Y - Miscellaneous (Box 682, Folder 4)
    - Z - Miscellaneous (Box 692, Folder 3)
  - Audiovisual materials, 37
    Sound recordings; Moving Images
    - Arts - Publications - American National Heritage Association - The Sound of Quinto Lingo FRENCH, 1977 November; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15642)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - NYCOM Graduation - Dr. Schure and Dr. Riland, VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11186)